onlineconversion.com 2003-12-04

# BlueSparks Network - Privacy Statement

 BlueSparks Network  **  

 Games I wrote   

 Sites in the works   
WeekendGladiator  
AceConvert

 Contact Info   

| 

## _The BlueSparks Network  
_Privacy Statement

For all sites in the BlueSparks Network

**BlueSparks** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our web sites.

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use server logs, which contain your IP address, to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The information in the server logs are used to generate reports to track our page views, page errors, and referrers. This information is used only by us.

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Contact information**

Some forms may ask users to give us contact information (email address).

  * **BlueSparks** : Contact information from the BlueSparks newsletter is administered by [ListBot](http://www.listbot.com/). The Chat and Tell-a-Friend scripts in use are for demostration purposes only and the information is not saved on our server.
  * **AcronymSearch** : Contact information from the add and request forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. This contact information is not required. After the add or request has been completed, the contact information is deleted.
  * **OnlineConversion** : Name and email is asked for in the Tell-a-Friend program. This information is not saved on our server and is used only for emailing your friend. Your Email address is asked when joining the mailing list. This information is saved on our server and used only for sending web page updates and occasional newsletters.
  * **LostJungle** : Name and email is asked for in the Tell-a-Friend program. This information is not saved on our server and is used only for emailing your friend.
  * **ComedyBarn.net** : Name and email is asked for in the Tell-a-Friend program. This information is not saved on our server and is used only for emailing your friend.Your Email address is asked when joining the mailing list. This information is saved on our server and used only for sending daily or weekly jokes for which you signed up.

**We will never give or sell your email address to anyone.**

**Web Forms**

**OnlineConversion.com:** Many of the forms ask you to enter information for using the conversions. Such as how many feet to convert to meters. Some may ask for personal information, such as your birthday, to tell you how many days old you are. These forms use "Client Side Scripting" and do not send any information to us. The information entered in these forms disappears as soon as you close your web browser. 

**AcronymSearch.com:** The information typed into the acronym search, and reverse acronym search, is sent to our server and may be saved. We would use this information for determining the "most popular" acronym or something similar. We consider this information to be "non-personal" in nature, and can in no way be associated with any single person. 

**Forums**

We use a community type BBS for our Message Forums.

If you post messages as a guest, your name and email address is asked for. This information can be viewed by anyone. Your email address is not required and we recommend not giving it, and using an alias for your name, if you do not wish this information available to the public.

If you register for the message forums, other personal information is asked for. This information is viewable by anyone. Most information is optional and we recommend not giving information you do not want available to the public. Your email address is required but you can make this private in your preferences. Your name is required but you may use an alias if you wish.

Any information you give in the message forums is not used by us. It is used only for the message forum. Some examples are notifying you through email when you request to be notified of postings.

**Chat**

BlueSparks has public chat which asks for your name. Anybody can view this information so BlueSparks recommends using an Alias when using the chat. The chat is for demostration purposes only for those interested in downloading the chat program.

**External Links**

These sites contain links to other sites. **BlueSparks** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**

These sites have standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We cannot be 100% sure that nobody can hack into our server, so BlueSparks recommends using a free e-mail service, such as hotmail, when submitting your e-mail address to sites on the Internet.

****

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of these sites, or your dealings with these Web sites, you can contact:
